Writer Fang Haowen's recent actions have drawn attention.
Experts advise
that the possibility of depression
or other mental distress cannot be ruled out.
They urge the public to be objective
and avoid stigmatization.
How is this depression?
Isn't he just crazy?
This is definitely not depression.
This is Bipolar disorder.
With depression, you hurt yourself first.
With Bipolar disorder, you hurt others, then yourself.
He might even end up killing himself.
I think you have a touch of Bipolar disorder.
Since when do I have Bipolar disorder?
Don't you have Bipolar disorder?
Don't make a scene here.
If we start fighting here,
neither of us will look good.
Then let's fight! Come on, hit me!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry! I'm sorry, honey!
My hair! My hair is gone!
Pick it up.
Mr. He... Mr. He! Mr. He!
Where can I find Mr. Fang?
I have a few questions for him.
The Wicked Outsider
A Final Letter to the World
Fang Haowen
A.k.a. The Solitary Chanter
This letter is what I leave to this world,
my final voice.
By the time you read these words,
I will have shed this mortal shell.
I've read the classics since childhood,
shouldering the mission to awaken the world.
Unappreciated and misunderstood.
After I'm gone,
my words
will one day be recognized by the world.
Then,
they will regret
their indifference and injustice toward me today.
Mr. He! Mr. He! It's Bie Fan!
Speak Mandarin!
I... It's Bie Fan.
You again?
Mr. Fang is trying to kill himself again!
He died again?
Are you sure?
I'm not sure.
If you're not sure, what the hell are you talking about?
But I saw his suicide note!
He wants to bury himself in his hometown!
Hachun City, Xing County, Fangjiatun, Yaolong Ridge.
The fifth mountain on the left,
halfway up, next to a tree.
Kid, listen to me.
Go to his hometown right now.
And then?
And then,
once you make sure he's dead,
call me to let me know, okay?
Okay.
Hey, Sihai.
Hey, Bie Fan.
Where are you?
I'm at the train station.
I'm at the train station too.
Where in the station?
At the ticket gate for Hachun.
Aren't we going back to Liaocheng?
Why are you over there?
Wait for me, I'll be right there.
Train 31 to Hachun
is now boarding.
Please hurry and line up to board.
Bie Fan! Bie Fan!
Where are you going?
Mr. Fang is going to kill himself.
I have to go and save him.
He's a total fraud.
You can't believe what he says anymore.
I read his suicide note.
It's definitely real.
But what if he really wants to kill himself?
What if he's really sick?
I'll just go check on him and come back.
Well, fine.
Then... then stay safe.
Here, take this to eat on the way.
Don't believe everything he says!
You hear me?
I hear you.
Bie Fan believes everything.
Is this you?
This is my best friend.
This young guy looks pretty sharp.
What did you buy?
Stinky tofu.
To the left of Yaolong Ridge,
halfway up the fifth mountain.
Where do we start counting from?
You fake-peddling crooks!
You'd even scam the dead!
I just got these glasses.
Who is it?
You scared me!
Oh my God!
Mr. Fang!
You can't die!
Mr. Fang! You can't die!
Mr. Fang!
I won't let you die!
You're choking me!
Let go!
Mr. Fang, come down!
Mr. Fang, you can't die!
Mr. Fang!
Mr. Fang! Fang!
Oh my God!
Mr. Fang!
You're okay now.
You're not going to die.
Why is it...
Why is it you again?!
Your mom...
My mom passed away.
You...
I'm fine.
My mom went to be with my dad.
It's just that...
Are you crazy?!
Aren't you the sick one?
What the hell do you want?!
I don't want you to die.
I want to die!
I can't let you die!
I just can't let you die!
I want to die! I want to die! I want to die!
I want to die!
No!
Get lost!
Let go!
Let... let go!
I want to die!
What's it to you if I want to die?
I...
I want to die!
Mr. Fang, your condition is getting worse again.
Get lost! Get lost!
You kicked my tombstone!
My Nothingness... how did my Nothingness disappear?
Where is the Nothingness?
Where is my Nothingness?
Is this it?
Come on, give me the Nothingness.
I'll give it to you if you don't kill yourself.
Give me the Nothingness!
Fine, I won't kill myself.
Come on, give me the Nothingness.
You... you've lied to me.
I don't believe you.
You even...
You...
Came, loved...
Plagiarized!
How can I die without my Nothingness?
Stop right there!
Stop! Give Nothingness back to me!
Oh my God!
Nothingness!
The flowers hadn't bloomed last time I was here.
Good thing it wasn't hot.
Or I would've been burned.
What are you doing?!
Seriously. Oh my god!
But this is spicy!
Where are the tissues?
Quick, wipe it off! Wipe it off!
Bie Fan
Bie Fan, come out!
I won't hit you anymore, Bie Fan.
Bie Fan!
Um, you two look at each other.
Kiss! Kiss!
Honey.
These canola flowers are really
beautiful!
Stop!
You think I won't
run right over your body?
Wedding photos, Honey.
Bee!
There's a bee!
Mr. Fang!
There's a bee! There's a bee, Mr. Fang!
There are bees.
If you didn't want us having hot pot, just say so!
Run!
There are bees!
Oh my God!
Bees! There are bees!
Why is this happening?
Are they only stinging me?
Are you guys crazy?
What's going on? Why are you running?
My face is burning!
I'm getting disfigured here!
He stole from me!
What did he steal?
He stole my "mei"—my Nothingness!
How many tons of coal did he steal?
Not coal!
The "mei" that means Nothingness!
If you have nothing, what did he steal?
I mean the word Nothingness!
I get it.
This young man must have stolen his money.
So he has no money to buy coal.
His pockets are completely empty.
What?
What? No!
You're making up a story!
No!
It's the...
The Nothingness in "The man of old is gone, the waters are cold today"!
He's sick.
Bipolar disorder.
Oh, he's sick just because you say so?
The farce of washed-up author Fang Haowen is escalating.
Experts claim he suffers from a mental illness.
He slapped judge Hei Cong,
author Ren Fangfang,
and even made a huge scene at a campus cafeteria,
holding filth to pollute the future of our nation.
Even if he's cured, he'll still be drooling.
Give me my Nothingness! Give it back!
He definitely has a serious illness, Honey.
Stay away from him!
Don't catch whatever he has!
It's fine. It's nothing.
Forget it. Just give it back.
I understand.
Even though we got dirty,
he is a sick man.
WeChat Pay received 500 yuan.
Thanks.
It's camping. We like it lively anyway.
I don't mind if you scan it or not.
Get that illness treated soon!
We understand!
WeChat Pay received 500 yuan.
Not enough.
Give me a little more.
WeChat Pay received 1,000 yuan.
Come again when you're free!
I need to use the bathroom.
I don't believe you.
I really need to use the bathroom.
Mr. Fang, I'm not a kid anymore.
Mr. Fang can't hold it anymore.
Mr. Fang, just tell me what you're trying to do.
I'm not falling for your tricks this time.
I need to use the bathroom.
The bathroom.
I've said it so many times.
Now do you believe me?
What's wrong with him?
He's sick.
Pretty seriously, too.
He's completely incontinent.
No, he has Bipolar disorder.
Mr. Fang, you don't need to be embarrassed.
Thank you.
No one has ever cared about me before.
That's why I got Bipolar disorder.
Now that I have you,
I feel like I'm cured.
Really?
You're a chef, right?
Yes, Mr. Fang.
I'm a chef.
Then what kind of dishes do you usually like to cook?
I can cook a lot of dishes.
My best dish is Squirrel Fish.
Squirrel Fish?
Is it the legendary Squirrel Fish?
Yes.
The one from Xiaoxiao Deyue Restaurant in Suzhou?
Squirrel Fish.
Tell me how you make it.
I want to hear the detailed recipe.
Right.
Squirrel Fish is a famous Jiangsu dish.
First, you need to prepare a fish,
about 750 grams.
Preferably a mandarin fish.
Then 18 grams of peeled shrimp.
15 green peas.
1,000 grams of refined lard.
And then...
Mr. Fang?
Mr. Fang...
Mr. Fang!
There you are!
I thought you ran away.
I'm not running.
A man should come into this world clean,
and when he leaves...
Well, he doesn't necessarily have to leave, right?
Through interacting with you all day,
I really feel much better.
Really?
Unlock me.
Let's go get a body scrub.
I can't unlock it.
You'll run away if I do.
Why would I run?
I, uh...
Isn't the wristband with you?
How could I... I don't have clothes.
How could I run out of here?
I'd be breaking the law!
Tell me how I could run away.
Treat me like your older brother.
Come on. Name one way.
Seems like you can't run.
Right.
Then I'll untie you.
You can't run.
I won't. I won't.
Untie me.
Bro,
you just mentioned some of
the ingredients to prepare.
So how exactly do you make Squirrel Fish?
Could you explain it in more detail?
Bro?
Then, after killing the mandarin fish,
descale and gut it.
And after washing it clean,
lay it flat on the cutting board.
First, chop off the fish head.
Make a cut at the top of the head.
Put the fish head aside.
Are you the attendant?
Come help me open a locker.
102.
Come on! Come here!
What's wrong?
Open the locker. I need my clothes.
Where's your wristband?
I...
By the way, Mr. Fang,
do you prefer sweet or savory?
Mr. Fang?
I took a dive and lost my wristband.
Hurry. My phone is inside.
I can't pay without it. Hurry!
Get lost!
You went to the bathroom without closing the door!
Mr. Fang?
Mr. Fang!
Why are you looking at my face?
I can't recognize you by your ass.
Mr. Fang!
Attendant!
What is it?
Did you see
the guy who was just with me?
The one who crapped his pants?
He left.
Without a key,
how did he open the door?
Sir, this is a public bathhouse.
Security isn't that tight.
Right here.
Let's make this quick.
Freedom
Roaming
Everywhere you go is a hazard to me,
yet I cannot stop your journey.
My only globe
has been ravaged by your footsteps,
Mr. Fang!
And...
"And..." Let me finish my poem!
"And..." Mr. Fang!
If you come any closer, I'll jump!
I'll jump right now!
Try me!
...and spins no more.
When one person
becomes another person's entire world,
time
becomes the manual for the end of the world.
Bie Fan.
Farewell.
Thank you.
I came into this world clean,
let me leave it clean.
Help me put Nothingness back.
Okay?
Mr. Fang, don't jump!
I'll return the word Nothingness to you.
Bie Fan.
It's okay if Nothingness is gone.
Just help me add it back.
Dad